Three magical wishes. One life changing adventure.
Wish Dragon is a animation, family, comedy film directed by Chris Appelhans.
Determined teen Din is longing to reconnect with his childhood best friend when he
meets a wish-granting dragon who shows him the magic of possibilities.
Din (voice), played by Jimmy Wong.
Long (voice), played by John Cho.
Mom (voice), played by Constance Wu.
Lina (voice), played by Natasha Liu Bordizzo.
Short Goon / Security Guard 2 (voice), played by Jimmy O. Yang.
Pockets (voice), played by Aaron Yoo.
Wish Dragon is a 2021 animated fantasy comedy film written and directed
by Chris Appelhans in his feature film directorial debut.
The film stars Jimmy Wong, John Cho, Constance
Wu, Natasha Liu Bordizzo, Jimmy O.
Yang, Aaron Yoo, Will Yun Lee, and Ronny Chieng.
Jackie Chan produced the film and voiced Cho's role
in the Chinese Mandarin version.
It tells the story about a college student named Din Song, who encounters a teapot
inhabited by a dragon named Long, who has the power to grant three wishes.
Wish Dragon was released theatrically in China on January 15, 2021,
and on Netflix internationally on June 11, 2021.
A sequel is set to be released in Summer 2027
with Appelhans returning as writer.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.